We are now at noon.
Good afternoon, everyone.
Good afternoon.
Wakato Yasumori.
I'm Mei Fujita from space.
I look forward to working with you.
You are from space, but how are things on Earth?
Today's weather is fine.
That's good. Thank you very much.
Okay, so this is the third one.
This is the third one.
Thank you very much for the special.
So, let's get right to it, shall we?
Please do so.
Okay, this is my last topic. I guess you could say it's a topic or an episode.
Family!
It's a family episode.
It's so heartwarming.
It's very heartwarming.
Thank you for everything.
Well, that's all for today.
I'd like to talk about the fact that all nine of you have brothers and sisters.
First of all, that's amazing, isn't it?
That's very rare, isn't it?
How about the day you look back?
I see you three times.
Yes, I mean...
So you don't have one of each.
Tork, you all have siblings.
And that's a lot of people.
I have three siblings.
I have a brother and sister.
I have a younger sister, and I'm the eldest.
I have a younger sister.
Family members, grandparents...
I'm the eldest.
I'll be a big supporter.It's going to be a great meritocracy.
I'm not sure why we're talking about this.
It was quite a while ago.
We all wanted to go to a private barbecue with our families.
"Let's go to a private barbecue
"Let's go to a private barbecue with our families.
Then we said, "Isn't that a lot of people?
And then we said...
Well then...
I was counting.
And there were 48 of us.
It was 48.
Then...
He said, "We're AKBs!
We're AKB group!
And we were like...
We said, "We can form a group.
Then who would be the center? I said.
I said.
I said, "Here's the drums.
I said, "Let's go with the one that's visible.
And he said...
Wait a minute.
Kazuki Yuna's dad said
Kazuki and Yuna's dad can meet him, too.
Ryubi and Yuna's dad
Shall we form a double center group?
I'll make a double center group.
and they had a good time.
It was decided!
We are from the Tohoku region of Japan.
But don't forget that if you add all of our family members
48 if we all join together as a family.
I hope you will stay with us.
We will do our best to make our debut one day.
We will do our best.
We'll come up with our own formation.We'll come up with the formation and everything.
We'll think of the direction and so on.
Including the potential
We will make the right decision.
When will it debut?
Is this the next one?
Yes, it is. Last topic.
Last topic.
What's next.
Important.
Important. Suddenly.
I'm serious.
We have made it this far after 8 years,
And this year we have Pacifico Yokohama,
We have a big wall to climb.
We are working hard to get to the Nippon Budokan,
We have been working hard to get to the Nippon Budokan, but we have to look forward to the future, because we have come this far with just the nine of us,
I have an announcement to make.
What a surprise,
Suddenly, there will be no new members.
Scary.
After 8 years in the business, things like that happen.
Don't worry.
I'm sure there are many things that will happen in the future,
Yes, I'm sure. There will be many scenes like this,
It will be fine with the members.
We will be fine.
Don't cry later.
I won't.
How was it?
Eight years.
Was it fast?
I wonder.
I don't know.
Maybe it was too late.Maybe it was too late.
It was late.
Everyone had been doing it since elementary school, so I definitely had to balance being a student and a talker,
It was quite difficult,
There were times when I was confused about who I was at school and who I am here.
Of course, I had to balance my private life as well, and that's how far I've come,
It was a long time.
Yes, it was. But I think that the members have not changed much over the years.
There has not been much turnover.
That is why I think it is a miracle,
I think we can make it with these 9 members.
Each and every one of us thinks so.
I think each and every one of you is thinking about it.
I think that is one of our strengths,
Moreover, Tork-san is so individualistic,
And they all have different tastes.
If they really like this, they like that,
The difference is obvious.
Each one of the members is different,
I think our strength lies in the fact that each one of us is different, but when all nine of us are combined, we become stronger than ever,
I hope that we can continue to celebrate our 9th and 10th anniversaries as the strongest 9 members,
I hope we can continue to celebrate our 9th and 10th anniversaries as the strongest 9 of us.
Thank you very much for watching.
Today, August 11, we will be celebrating our 8th anniversary.
We will be performing at Mina World in Yamagata Prefecture for the 8th anniversary of our 8th anniversary!
Yay!
Yes, that's right, the anniversary live is an annual event.
That's right!
We are having an event called "Happy 8th Anniversary".
I wonder if they use water or something...
I wonder... after this.
Right...
We always use water for our anniversary events.
I'm looking forward to seeing what kind of live performance it will be.
This year, it's an amusement park.
We've had Evins and others do it before, but we're taking it to a higher level.
We're going to take it to the next level.
Let's have fun together!Yes, I'm looking forward to it, and I hope you all enjoy it with me.
Let's have fun together!
If you're watching this video, please come visit us sometime.
Please do!
Why don't you come to our world and have a good night, too?
Come here, come here, come here.
Come here, Tohoku
Come here, come here.
I'm waiting for the commercial.
I'll be waiting.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm about to see who's waiting in line.
Oh, yes.
Oh, sure.
While standing in line...
If you're in line, please raise your hand.
Raise your hand if you're in line.
Raise your hand and be my friend
I'd like you to raise your hand if you're in line.
That's one way to make friends.
Yes, there is.
I look forward to working with you.
by H.
Yes, we released our 3rd mini-album THE TALK on August 9!
Here it is. What a cute jacket! It's really nice, isn't it?
How much is it?
It's only 2,000 yen!
That's cheap!
You can buy it with two bills?
What do you mean? Two Hideyos!
Two Shudai!
Two Xiujais?
Yes, you can buy it with two XiuDai, gentlemen.
Because one and one together is one, right?
Yes, one and one together is two.
Two, yes.
Yes, that's right.
This is another variety, ladies and gentlemen.This album is rich in variety.
I hope you will listen to this album as much as possible.
I hope you will listen to it as much as possible.
Thank you very much.
Shudai announced!
What is it?
Tissues are ready!
Wipe your tears with this.
Yes, I'll wipe them with this.
We
December 29th.
At the end of the year
At Ashikura Yokohama
We will be having an Oichiron Live!
[Applause]
Yes our 8th anniversary is all packed everything is everything is everything is everything is everything is everything yes here 4 8 groups may be announced
We're going to have a lot of lunches, a lot of names, a lot of people...
I am looking forward to seeing you all at Inari Tohoku's Pacifico Yokohama on December 29th.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for a wonderful interview.
We've never met before.
We're meeting for the first time. We'll be in a group together.
We'll be in a group together.
That's how it all started. It's heavy.
Thank you very much.
We've talked a lot about Inari and Mokuyosan.
I hope we can all work together for a long time to come.
I hope we can all do our best for a long time to come, so please take good care of Tomoyasu-san.
So, please give your best regards to Inari Tokomoyasan.
And that's Inari Toku-san's Kazuka Yasumori and Yuu at Fizz Ten.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!
Pompi said he's doing it, he won't go.